http://www.henry.com/privacy-policy

California Transparency Act
Purchase Order Terms and Conditions (Suppliers)
California Transparency Act
Purchase Order Terms and Conditions (Suppliers)
Dealer Locator
Let us help you find the right building envelope solution for your project.
SEARCH
Privacy policy
Your privacy on the Internet is important to us. Because we gather certain types of information about the users of the network of sites and services of Henry Company ("Henry"), we believe you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it. You are responsible for keeping your own e-mail address, username, and password confidential.
Information Collection and Use
Henry is the sole owner of the personal information collected on this web site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Henry collects information from our users at several different points on our web sites. Wherever we collect personal information, we include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. When you register with one of our sites, Henry may ask for your contact information (such as your e-mail address) and your demographic information (such as your zip code, industry and job function). We use demographic information to tailor your experience at our web site, showing you content and advertisements that we think might interest you. Henry may also ask for such information at other times, such as when you request information or when you decide to purchase products or services from Henry and/or our customers and suppliers. Henry will not disclose any of your personal information, except as described in this Privacy Policy, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or to protect the rights or property of Henry. The information collected by Henry may be used in a number of ways. For example, Henry will share broad aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. An example would be where Henry provides partners and advertisers with information about the percentage of men or women who visit our sites, or about the types of industries that users are interested in. Henry's goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with the most personalized web experience possible and with an efficient means to reach the right audience and know their needs. By knowing a little about you, Henry is able to deliver more relevant content, and hence a better service, to you.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information associated with the user. We use cookies to be reminded of who you are and to access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service. This cookie is set when you register. Henry uses cookies on our sites to help track visits and process the items in your shopping basket. Cookies are also used to estimate our audience size. Each browser accessing Henry is given a unique cookie, which is then used to determine repeat usage versus initial usage, and to help in targeting ads based on user interests.
IP Addresses
We use IP addresses for purposes of system administration, and to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
Links
This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Henry is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
Notification of Changes; Conflicts
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we would notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. This page reflects the most up-to-date version of our privacy policy, and thus takes precedence over information provided in other documents.
Tools
Henry_homepage icons
CustomerCare
Untitled-1
KnowledgeCenter
Untitled-1
DocumentSearch
Copyright© 2020 Henry Company. All rights reserved.
